UNITE Organizing Department Records 6000/039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Organizing Department Records
1940-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/039
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes files of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) and the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU).
5757932
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Textile industry, New York (State); Clothing workers, Labor unions.; Textile workers, Labor unions.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); UNITE HERE (Organization); Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Organizing Department; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union -- Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Organizing Department --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) -- Archives
5757932
- Ames - Fieldcrest Cannon (Box 1)
  - BMP - Listo of Workers Mtg Poss. ULPs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ames, Leesport, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Angelica Co. File, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ARC Contract, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ARC Fulton, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Autoliv - Research File, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Autoliv 1994 Midwest (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barneys Campaign, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "We Are Barney" Daily News, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Barney's 1996/ Negot. Notes/ Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barneys Lit. 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Barneys Bargaining1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Membership Lists, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Barneys, '96 Press, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barneys, 1996, Non-Union (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lyndhurst, D.C., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barneys, '96 Bankruptcy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Broadway, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Brooks 2001, NLRB (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Brooks Brothers/ Short Hills, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Brooks Brothers Members, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brooks Brothers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brooks, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo Laundry, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Certech, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Claritian C&Cs, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Columbia Textile, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Churchill Linen Service, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cole-Haan, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ConCo RockHill,SC Southern July 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Costume Builders, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - D.P. Opelika, AL Summer '96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Danaklan, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Danvid Co., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Discount Auto Part - D.C. 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dillards, Little Rock, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Duane Read Aug/ Sept 2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Duane Reade Gotv, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Rochester Eldre Components, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Epic Components C&Cs Aug 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cannon 92, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Fieldcrest Expenses Proposed Budgets, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Fieldcrest 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - FC Nov. Staff Needs, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cannon Certificates, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fieldcrest Cannon, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Fieldcrest, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Fieldcrest Cannon 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fieldcrest - Vote, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cannon 1999 - Company Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Salisbury Post, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Fieldcrest, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Southern Regional Joint Board, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 1998 Fieldcrest - Cannon (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Fieldcrest Cannon, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Fingerhut - Oceanside (Box 2)
  - Fingerhut, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Flambeau Air mold, NC, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Flex New Philadelphia Ohio C&Cs, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Flexell Topeka, Kansas - Southwest, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Forstmann July 1995 Georgia (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Foto J, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Foxpoint Recognition S.W. Jan 95, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fruit of the Loom Harlingen, Texas 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Guess, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gabriel Ride Control Oklahoma Spring 1995 SW (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Textiles Southern Region March 95 Loss 5/25/95, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - GRI Feb. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - GRI 1996 Shut Down After Blitz (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Back-to-School Boycott GUESS, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Guess Rally - Miami 12/5/97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Press Clippings, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Guess:, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Religious/Guess, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Working Lists Guess, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lists of Orgs, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - H&P Industries Jan. 95 Midwest, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hope Webbing New England Lost Election, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - JCG Chicago May 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Jonbil South Boston, Va Midatlantic July 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Kmart, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kohl's, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Koch Spring, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LEAR, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Levis Lit/Manage, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - LS&Co Organizing Plan, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - LS&Co El Paso Gen. Org. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Levis Focus Groups, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Levis, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Levis, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Lochmann's Paper (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lumex, Inc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Unite Leaflets - National Linen, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Marshall's, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Marshall's, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Manhattan Beer Dist. Jan 97 Leaflets, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Miami Dade Probed - Don't Run 1996 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Miami Street Vendors Spring 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mobile Co. File, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Morse Automotive June 1995 SW (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Morse & Petit Jean (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Manhattan Beer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Linen Press Releases, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - National Linen (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Pay Stubs - N. Linen, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - NL Louisville Pics, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - NL Arrow (Ny) Pics, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - NL Scranton-Aramark Pics (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - NL Churchill (MA) Pics (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - NL FDR (FL) Pics, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - NL Amer. Eagle (NJ) Pics, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - NL Portland, ME Pics, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Nursing Homes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Oceanside Co. File (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Paragon - Whiting (Box 3)
  - Paragon, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    2 floppy discs
  - Paragon (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Paragon, Co. Lit., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Paragon (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Paragon, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Polymers Vermont New England JHBI, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Laundry Purity Services New Bedford, MA New England Jt. Bd., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Peerless Actions - Press, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Leaflets - Peerless 11/95, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Montreal - Peerless, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Peerless Rallies, N.W., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Plastic Decorating, Inc, C&Cs, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - PK USA Midwest May '95, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Petit Jean Poultry - SW June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - USA Polymer, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Retail - Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1995 and 1996 RETAIL Organization Program, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bergdorf Goodman, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Local 340 Contacts, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Retail Probes 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Petitioning, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UNITE Retail Org (Canada), 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Rauch So. Reg. Aug. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Richmark New England Fall '96, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Roadmaster, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Roadmaster Beloit WI Midwest July 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Aristocrat Knoxville, TN Southern 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rockline Industries Sheboygan, WI Midwest, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Safelight Enfield, NC Southern 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Schottenstein, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Shape Maine Spring 1995 New England (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Springs Decort Aug 1995 Southern (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Schelgel - Raidsville Recognition Fall 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Smith Enterprise Jan 95 Southern, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Stone Construction, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Sun Engine Election Oct. 1993 Texas Closed! (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Tartan textile Services, Inc. Co. File, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Tandy Brands, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Local 218 Textile Processors Co. Files, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Today's Menu, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Transtech Baltimore June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Trend - Lines, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Tricon Columbia, Missouri Southwest July 1995 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Tultex 1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Tultex Sweing March '95, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - UG Arc Co. File, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - UCP, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Unclaimed Freight 6/94 PS Jt. Bd., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Up to Date, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Whiting - Clinton, MA Blitzed - no Campaign N.Eng. Jt Bd., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Campaigns Started Before MV here, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Mt. Vernon Mills, Trion, GA '94 ILGWU, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- ACTWU Organizing manuals and pamphlets, 1957-1995; TWUA J. P. Stevens clippings, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - ACTWU Organizing manual, Part 1 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Flyers Protesting non-union garment sales 1957-1963, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ACWA pamphlets and flyers protesting imports, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Organizing Leaflets and Pamphlets, 1940-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Flyers and Pamphlets, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ACTWU Sample Leaflets and Illustrations 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sample Leaflets and Illustrations, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "The Stevens Worker": ACTWU Newsletter 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ACTWU Organizing manual, Part 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)